本字幕由YYeTs字幕组原创翻译
www.ZiMuZu.tv 欢迎交流
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    ustvboom
了解最新影视字幕发布信息
饥饿
的青春
第二季  第二集
这号码是谁
I don't know this number.
喂
Hello?
我是加比  你没必要装男声
It's Gabi, you don't have to use the fake voice.
我从中国回来了  玩得超开心
I'm back from China and I had an amazing time!
天啊  你什么毛病啊
Oh, my god, what is wrong with you?
我三周都没你的消息了
I haven't heard from you in three weeks!
对不起  但你知道
I'm sorry, but do you know
国际手机套餐要多少钱吗
how much international cell phone plans cost?
好几千呢  甚至都不能查看留言
Thousands! You can't even check your messages.
等等  你没查看留言吗
Wait a second, you never checked your messages?
没有  怎么了  你给我留了言吗
Uh, no. Why? Did you leave me one?
没有  但如果有人留言了  你什么时候会听到
No. Uh, but if someone did, when would you be hearing them?
我拿到行李后
Uh, when I get my luggage.
来接我吧  我得挂了
Come pick me up. I gotta go.
有个人说如果我带他的包过海关
This guy said I could borrow his phone
他就把电话借给我用
if I carried his bag through customs,
我刚看到了一个指示牌说不该这样做
and I just read a sign that said I should not do that.
这号码是谁
Don't know this number.
喂
Hello?
乔什  我是索菲亚
Josh, it's Sofia.
加比从中国回来了  她刚从机场给我打来电话
Gabi's back from China. She just called me from the airport,
她没有收到你的留言
and she never got your message.
什么
W-what?
她的手机一直关机
Her phone was off the whole time.
她没有拒绝你  只是没收到你的留言
Look, she didn't reject you, she just never got your message.
天啊  那她没必要听了
Oh my god, then she never has to hear it!
你为什么不想要她听
Why would you not want her to hear it?
因为我是个有羞耻心的人类吗
Because I'm a human being who can experience shame?
我一直都在绞尽脑汁
Look, I've been racking my brain
好让我们见面时
trying to figure out a way to make this less awkward
没那么尴尬  现在没那个必要了
when I see her, and now I don't have to.
有的  她有权利听那段留言
Yes, you do! She has a right to hear that message!
尴尬的长留言
That long, awkward message.
不  我们都翻篇了  一切都改变了
No. She's moved on, I've moved on, everything's changed.
你说"一切都改变了"是什么意思
What do you mean "everything's changed"?
两周纪念日愉快
Happy two-week anniversary.
那是谁
Who's that?
到底是谁
Who is that?
十五分钟后在机场见
I'll meet you at the airport in 15 minutes.
十六分钟后在机场见
I'll meet you at the airport in 16 minutes.
乔什  你得告诉她你的感受
Josh, you have to tell her how you feel.
我不用
No, I don't.
那是三周之前的事了
That was so three weeks ago.
反正她开机之后
But she's going to hear the message
也会听到那通留言啊
when she turns on her phone anyway.
我给她买部新手机的话就不会
Not if I get her a new phone.
怎么买啊
How's that gonna happen?
因为每个机场都有...
Because in every airport, there's a...
我爱美国
I love America.
翻译  冰蓝 aaaBao roaddog
索菲亚
Sofia!
欢迎回家  见到你真好
Welcome home! It's so good to see you!
校对  roaddog
我也是
You too!
虽然我会怀念方圆十英里内
Though I will miss being the only blonde
时间轴  aaaBao
就我一个金发妞的感觉
in a 10-mile radius.
最近出了什么事  我错过了什么
So, what's going on? What did I miss?
后期  斯人   总监  roaddog
没什么  大家都闭嘴
Nothing! Nothing, everybody shut up.
乔什  你好  你在这里干什么呢
Josh, hi! What are you doing here?
我们大家都在这里干什么呢
What are any of us doing here?
这个问题每天都困扰着我
Really, that's the question that haunts me every day.
感觉怎么样  这辈子最棒的时光
So, how was it? Best time of your life?
绝妙  超赞  精彩吗
Killer, awesome, amazing?
是啊  太完美了
Yes, it was absolutely perfect.
听见了吗  索菲亚
Hear that, Sofia?
听见了
Yes, I do.
是因为你喜欢库珀  还是中国
Perfect because you like Cooper, or China?
都有
Both.
不  选一个  必须选一个
No, pick one. You have to pick one.
好吧  那就是库珀
Uh, okay. Cooper then.
他很棒  性感自信
I mean, he's amazing. He's sexy, he's confident,
了解中国的一切
and he knows everything about China.
中国人还问他
Chinese people were asking him
哪里有最好吃的中餐
where to find the best Chinese food.
她的意思是  跟库珀在一起很开心
What she's saying is she's happy with Cooper.
所以没什么好说的了  除了...
So, there's nothing left to say except, shwah!
一台新手机
A new phone?
你为什么要买  我的就在这里
Why'd you do that? I have mine right here.
你没必要开机的  没必要
You don't have to turn that on, no.
为什么
Why not?
你离开的时候
While you were gone,
有一种手机病毒席卷了全国
there was a phone virus that swept the country.
各地人们都面对面的交谈  可怕极了
People everywhere were talking face-to-face. It was horrible.
但是别担心
But, hey, no worries.
我会把你旧手机上的东西
I'll just transfer the stuff
传到新手机上
from your old phone to your new phone.
你明天来上班的时候来拿吧
You can grab it tomorrow when you come to work,
还可以跟吉莉见个面
and then you can meet Jilly.
吉莉  你养了只猫吗
Jilly! Aww, did you get a kitty?
不  我有了个女朋友
No. I got a girlfriend.
真快啊
That was fast.
我和吉莉之前在技术大会上就认识了
No, me and Jilly met a while ago at this tech conference,
这让她显得有点书呆
which makes her sound kind of nerdy,
但其实不是  她超级聪明
but she's not, she's just super smart,
超级性感  我提到她是选美冠军了吗
and like, really hot. Did I mention she's a beauty queen?
总之  她发现我和卡洛琳分手了
Anyway, she found out me and Caroline broke up,
就给我发了一条脸书消息  其他的都是历史了
and she sent me this Facebook message, and the rest is history.
瞧瞧  我们都好幸福啊
Well, would you look at that, we are all so happy!
就是啊  你有库珀  我有吉莉
I know, right? Like, you have Cooper, I have Jilly,
-索菲亚有...  -新手机
- Sofia has-- - A new phone.
只要你调到静音[保密]
As long as you keep it on silent.
他是这样让头发竖起来的啊
Oh, so that's how he gets his hair to stand on end.
我还以为他只用看见镜子里自己的裸体呢
I figured he just looked at himself in the mirror naked.
顺便说一句  尤兰达  我一直想谢谢你
By the way, Yolanda, I've been meaning to thank you.
谢什么
For what?
没穿裙子
Not wearing a skirt.
好了  搞定
All right, done.
我刚把加比旧手机里的
I just transferred everything
一切东西传到了我的电脑上
from Gabi's old phone onto my laptop,
然后传到了她的新手机上
then loaded it onto her new phone.
除了那段尴尬的留言  现在没人会听到了
Except that awkward message, which now no one will hear.
我取消婚礼之后
After I called off my wedding,
想见的人是你  加比
you're the one I wanted to see, Gabi.
我甚至去你家  拿着玫瑰跑上逃生梯
I even drove to your house climbed up your fire escape with roses
重现《风月俏佳人》里的情景
to Pretty Woman you.
现在没人会听见了
Now, no one will hear it.
帅气的擦窗工来了
Ooh, here comes that fine window washer.
他任何时候都能来"擦"我
He can squeegee me any day.
拜托  搞得好像你有机会似的
Please, like you have a chance.
这楼里一半的女性都想被他"擦"
Half the women in the building want to get "squeegeed" by him.
滚粗
Get out.
你好
Hi!
你真性感
You are hot.
大家好
Hey, guys!
我从中国回来了  心情好到飞起了
Back from China, never looked finah.
还以为你一去不复返了呢  亲爱的
Seems like you've been gone forever, baby!
真的吗  我已经觉得你回来得太久了
Really? It already seems like you've been back forever.
中国之旅如何
So, how was your trip?
中国太棒了  无论走到哪里
China was amazing! Everywhere we went,
我们都得到了贵族般的礼遇
they treated us like royalty.
他们都以为我是凯莉·安德伍德
Of course, they all thought I was Carrie Underwood.
美国著名乡村歌手
给你
Here you go.
我把你所有的资料都导进去了
I transferred all your info.
所有你需要听的留言也都导进这部手机里了
And all the messages you need to hear are in this phone.
太好了  谢谢  乔什
Great. Okay, thanks, Josh.
这顿早饭是为了欢迎我回来吗
Is this a welcome back breakfast?
算是吧  这顿丰盛的佳肴是由吉莉掌厨的
Kinda. This magnificent feast is courtesy of Jilly.
你的新女友
The new girlfriend.
唯一的女友
The one and only.
你就是加比吧  你真可爱
You must be Gabi. Aren't you cute as a button!
你好  很高兴见到你
Hi, it's really nice to meet you.
我借用了下你的一条围裙
I borrowed one of your aprons,
-希望你别介意  -当然不会
- I hope you don't mind. - Oh, of course not.
太好了  快请坐
Good. Now, come sit your sweet buns down
趁热吃点我做的早餐吧
and have some of my sweet buns while they're still warm.
好的
Okay.
我一直以为我讨厌会做饭的姑娘
I always thought I hated all girls who cooked.
事实证明  只讨厌你而已
Turns out, just you.
真好吃
These are really good.
每次我做华夫饼的时候  我通常会配...
You know, whenever I make waffles, I usually make--
炸鸡吗
Fried chicken?
还好我一直在健身
Good thing, I've been going to the gym.
看起来大家都很喜欢你做的饭
Seems like everybody really loves your cooking.
还喜欢别的  对吧
Among other things, huh?
好吧
Okay. Well, um...
谢谢你招待大家  吉莉
Thanks for keeping everybody well-fed, Jilly,
但现在还是我来吧
But I think I'll just take it from here.
好了  确认了
All right, we're confirmed.
奥斯丁来的研发小组
That development team from Austin
明晚会过来吃晚餐
is coming here for dinner tomorrow night.
太棒了  做什么菜呢
Excellent! Any thoughts on the menu?
做鸡肉馅饼怎么样
How about chicken pot pie?
抱歉  我习惯给乔什做饭了
Sorry. I just got so used to cooking for Josh,
还以为他在问我
I thought he was talking to me.
不  他是问我  因为我是大厨
No, he was talking to me, 'cause, you know, I'm the chef.
大厨当然是你
Of course you are,
但吉莉做晚餐也没关系啊
but I don't see why Jilly can't make the dinner.
因为我的工作就是做晚餐啊
Because it's my job to cook the dinner?
但你请了三周假
But, you've been gone for three weeks.
这话什么意思
Well, what does that mean?
情况有点变化了嘛
You know, things changed a little bit.
从你和你的男友
Since you went on vacation
去中国  度了三周假起
with your boyfriend to China for three weeks.
但你同意我去的
But, you said I could go.
我同意是因为你要求的
I said you could go because you asked me.
好吧  但现在我回来了
Okay, but now I'm back.
现在我有了女友  而且她喜欢烹饪
And now I have a girlfriend, and she likes to cook.
所以如果她想做晚餐  就能做
So, if she wants to make the dinner, she can.
谢谢你  亲爱的
Aww, thanks, baby.
我太高兴了
Fun.
你为什么不跟能干我活的人约会
Why can't you date somebody who can do my job?
你绝对不会相信乔什跟我说了什么
You are never gonna believe what Josh just told me.
谢天谢地  终于说了
Oh, thank God, finally!
你知道这事吗
You know?
我知道是大事  但不知道什么事
I know that it's something big, and that I don't know it.
所以  说吧
So, tell me.
明晚乔什有个商务晚宴
Josh is having a business dinner tomorrow night,
吉莉想负责做菜
and Jilly wants to cook it,
他还同意了
and he's letting her.
就这事  吉莉
That's what this is about? Jilly?
是啊  看见没  她在我的地盘上撒野
Yeah, can't you see? She's moving in on my territory!
用她的翘臀和迷人的口音
With her sweet buns and that adorable accent,
我恨她
argh, I hate her!
你的地盘吗  我以为你放下乔什了
Your territory? I thought you were over Josh?
你选择了库珀  和他在一起很幸福
You picked Cooper. You're happy with Cooper.
是的  是很幸福
Yes, I am happy with Cooper
我很高兴我选择了库珀
and I'm glad I picked Cooper,
我只是不满意乔什选择了吉莉
I'm just not glad that Josh picked Jilly.
她想要抢我工作啊
I mean, she's trying to take over my job!
天呐  给我详细讲下整件事
Oh, my God. Well, I want to hear all about it.
但你能先把鞋脱了
But first, can you take your shoes off
放到新的鞋架上吗
and put them on the new shoe rack?
你走之后我养成了这个习惯  所以...
I started it while you were gone, so...
天呐  我走之后怎么一切都变了呢
God, has everything changed since I left?
说真的  加比  脱鞋
Okay, seriously, Gabi. Shoes.
我走了三周
I mean, I'm gone three weeks,
乔什有了女友  你买了鞋架
and Josh has a girlfriend, and you have a shoe rack.
好了  不过一顿晚餐而已
Okay, it is just one dinner.
不  没那么简单
No. No, no, no.
做了一顿就会有第二顿
First it's one dinner, then it's two,
然后加比再见  他的饮食她全包了
then it's bye-bye Gabi, and she's cooking for him all the time!
这是一顿欢送餐
This is a gateway dinner!
你时差还没倒回来  你得睡会
Well, you are cracked out on jet lag, and you need some sleep.
不  你知道我想做什么吗
No. No, you know what I need?
我想把吉莉卷进地毯里
I need to roll Jilly up in a carpet
把她从桥上扔下去
and toss her off a bridge!
是  我现在懂了
Yes, now I hear it.
我时差没倒回来
I am cracked out on jet lag.
我要给库珀打个电话  然后睡一会
I'm gonna call Cooper, and take a little nap.
加比  你能把你的...
Hey, Gabi, could you, um... take your--
谢谢
Thank you.
你没事吧  亲爱的
You okay, sugar?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
就是睡不着
Just having a hard time sleeping.
我知道原因
I know what's going on.
虽然我怕说出来
Though, I'm afraid to say it
让你觉得我没安全感  但是...
because I don't want you to think I'm insecure. But...
我没安全感
I'm insecure.
你吗
You?
你担心什么呢
What are you insecure about?
我担心  不过才过去三周
The truth is, it's only been three weeks,
我觉得好像你还想着她
and I just feel like you might still be hung up on her.
相信我  我忘掉她了
Trust me. I'm over her.
她翻篇了  我也翻篇了
She's moved on, I've moved on.
说出她名字没什么大不了的
It's okay to say her name.
你的前未婚妻卡洛琳
Your ex-fiancée Caroline.
卡洛琳吗
Caroline?
对  卡洛琳
Yes. Caroline.
我想忘掉的是她  非常想
That's who I'm over. Very over.
现在开始  只有我们两个
From now on, it's just the two of us.
和楼下那个私闯民宅的人
And whoever's trying to break in downstairs.
加比  你在干什么  现在才早上三点
Gabi, what are you doing here? It's 3:00 in the morning.
中国可不是
Not in China.
你也知道那句话的
And, you know what they say,
早起的鸟儿有鸡煮
the early bird gets to cook the bird.
对吗
Right?
没人说过
No one says that.
我们说好的
We've discussed this.
我女朋友来做晚餐
My girlfriend is cooking the dinner.
你"女朋友"
Your "girlfriend."
你干嘛要这么比划我女朋友
Why did you put my girlfriend in quotes?
干嘛要这么比划我女朋友
不知道  乔什
I don't know, Josh,
或许是因为三周前你还准备结婚
maybe because three weeks ago you were engaged,
现在却又有了...
and now you have a...
首先  这不关你的事  你是我厨师
First of all, this is none of your business, you are my chef.
既然我是你厨师  那饭就该我做
If I am your chef, then I should be making the dinner.
你看起来是像在做晚餐
Kind of looks like you are making the dinner.
我做吗  谢谢
I am? Oh, thank you!
她做吗
She is?
不  她不做
No, she's not.
她要回家去
She's going home.
我们要睡觉去
We're going to bed.
亲爱的  等我一下哈
Sweetie, just give me one second.
我马上就来
I'll be up in a jiff.
亲  抱歉让你担心
Hon, I'm sorry that I worried you so much
觉得自己非来不可
you felt like you had to come over here.
但事情是这样的  乔什和我才开始恋爱
But, here's the thing. Josh and I are in a new relationship,
我觉得他似乎还有些念着前任
and I think he may be a little hung up on his ex still,
所以我想使劲浑身解数赢得他的心
so I'm using every biscuit in my basket to win him over.
你理解的  对吗
You understand, right?
是啊  绝对理解
I do, yeah, I totally do.
但问题是  我需要这份工作
But, here's my thing: I need this job.
显然我们有问题了
Well, appears we have a situation.
没错
Appears we do.
你觉得该怎么解决
How do you suggest we remedy that?
不如我们都做顿晚餐
Well, how about we both cook the dinner
看乔什更喜欢谁的
and we see which one Josh likes the best.
你想斗饭哈  没问题
If you're asking for a cook-off, you got one.
好  如果我赢了  晚餐我做
Okay, well, if I win, then I cook the dinner,
你离我厨房远一点
and you stay out of my kitchen.
如果我赢  晚餐我来
And if I win, I cook the dinner,
还有从今以后任何我想做的晚餐
and any other dinner I want to from now on.
在乔什的厨房里做
In Josh's kitchen.
-来战  -来
- Game on! - So on!
我们等天亮吧
Let's wait till the sun comes up.
-很好  -好
- Good idea. - Okay.
闻起来好香啊
Ooh, something smells good in here.
谢谢
Thank you.
她是在跟我说话
She was talking to me!
疯狂的白妞们啊
Crazy white girls.
看看你
Look at you.
我不知道谁更辛苦呢  你还是你的塑身裤
I don't know who's working harder, you or those spanx.
塑身裤
The spanx.
再多吃一颗炸虾球它的纽扣就会撑爆
I am one popcorn shrimp away from blowing a button
砸死一个人
and killing the man.
我还是想不通你怎么能
I still don't know how you got a date
跟全世界最性感的擦窗工约会
with the world's sexiest window washer.
我们心有灵犀
We have a connection.
光靠手势就能交流
We were able to communicate with just our hands.
真有爱  擦窗工
Oh, that's cute, window man.
不过我们还是用嘴说吧
But, let's talk with our voices now.
等会再"上手"
We can talk with our hands later.
你知道我是听障  对吗
You know I'm deaf, right?
不
No.
我不知道
No, I did not.
等等
Hold on.
他是听障  我该怎么办
He's deaf. What do I do?
跟他出去呀  他那么性感
Go out with him. He's hot.
但我从来没跟听障约会过
But, I've never been out with a deaf guy before.
所以呢  你也没跟帅哥约会过啊
So? You've never been out with a hot guy before.
我们要怎么交流啊
How are we supposed to communicate?
我们为什么要小声说  他听不见啊
Why are we whispering? He can't hear us.
我会读唇语  美女
I can read lips, mamacita.
看看  你终于有个会读东西的约会对象呢
Well, look at that, you finally have a date who can read.
这是今晚赴宴的人员调查
Here's the research on the guys coming to dinner tonight.
只有一个还算帅
Only one of them is cute.
你想出办法确保我
Did you figure out a way to make sure
能选中吉莉的馅饼了吗
I pick Jilly's pie over Gabi's pie?
我们能别说"馅饼"这词了吗
Can we please stop talking about their pies?
俚语暗指女性私处
我都要干呕了
It's making me dry heave.
我说真的
I'm serious.
我必须选出吉莉的
I need to pick Jilly's.
很简单  吉莉用紫红色瓷盅
It's easy. Jilly's using the aubergine ramekin,
加比用黄绿色
Gabi's using the chartreuse.
你能说一遍直男版吗
Can you say that again in hetero?
吉莉是紫的  加比是绿的
Jilly's purple, Gabi's green.
瓷盅就是烤馅饼的小碗
And a ramekin's a small dish you bake in.
懂了
Gotcha.
谁赢有什么关系
Why does it matter who wins?
因为吉莉开始觉得没有安全感
Because Jilly's starting to feel insecure.
担心我还想着加比
She's worried that I'm not over Gabi.
卡洛琳  担心我还想着卡洛琳
Caroline. She's worried I'm not over Caroline.
所以我要选出她的馅饼  证明我喜欢加比
So, I have to pick Jilly's pie to prove that I'm into Gabi.
吉莉  我喜欢吉莉  吉莉
Jilly! I'm into Jilly! Jilly, Jilly!
绿的是谁来着
Who's green again?
好了  我们首先蒙上你眼睛
Okay, first we have to blindfold you.
不要  为什么要蒙上
No. Why do I have to be blindfolded?
昨晚你也没在意啊
Didn't seem to bother you last night.
这不是一回事
This is so not that.
好了  开始吧
Okay, here we go.
太好吃了
So good.
第二个
And, number two.
也很好吃
Also delicious.
所以  你选哪个
So, which do you choose?
我选哪个
Which one do I choose?
快选一个
Just pick one!
好吧
Fine.
我...选...
I... pick...
第一个
the first one.
-是我的  -什么
- That's mine. - What?
我赢了  打败了专业厨师
I won! I beat a professional chef.
你选了我的  亲爱的
You picked mine, sweetie!
谢天谢地
Thank god.
恭喜  你赢的光明正大
Well, congrats. You won fair and square.
别气馁  加比  第二名没什么不好的
Chin up, Gabi. There's no shame in being runner-up.
起码别人这么说
Or so I've been told.
加比  等等
Gabi, wait.
给
Here.
带个我的馅饼走吧
Take one of my pies.
高热量的食物  能给人愉悦感
你看着似乎需要点暖心美食
It looks like you could use a little bit of comfort food.
谢谢
Thanks.
这么早就回来了  约会不顺吗
You're back early. It didn't work out?
是的
No, it did not.
或许下次你该跟个视障约会
Well, maybe next time you should date a blind guy.
怎么了
What happened?
买单的时候  他想要AA
When the check came, he wanted to go dutch.
我不怪他  我见过你能吃多少
I can't blame him. I've seen how much you can eat.
然后  他用半价券付了自己那一半
And then, he paid for his half with a two-for-one coupon.
你该甩了他这抠门又性感的家伙
You gotta dump his cheap, but well-sculpted ass.
不行  他会觉得我歧视听障的
I can't. He'll think I'm prejudiced against the deaf.
但我只是歧视抠门
But, I'm just prejudiced against the cheap.
没错  如果谁想尝你的甜头
Yeah. If a man wants your milk,
他得接受你这一整只大奶牛
he's gotta buy the whole cow.
除了不吃乳制品的盖瑞  我要说晚餐很成功
Except for no-dairy Gary, I'd say dinner was a hit.
我说你才成功
I'd say you were a hit.
我喜欢你选的歌
I like the music you picked.
真的吗  那再放
Really? Let's turn it up.
能请你跳支舞吗  女士
May I have this dance, m'lady?
又帅舞技又好啊
Aww, handsome, and he can dance.
还没到精彩部分呢
Wait till thriller comes on.
加比  我是从机场
Hey, Gabi, I'm calling you from...
-不不不  -给你打的电话
- No, no, no, no! - The airport, actually.
在我昨晚取消婚礼以后
Last night, after I called off my wedding,
-不是这首  -想见的人是你
- Wrong song. - You're the one I wanted to see.
-这是...  -我甚至去了你家
- This is... - I even drove to your house
拿着玫瑰爬上逃生梯  想...
and climbed up your fire escape with roses to--
刚才到哪了
So, where were we?
-天啊  -不  听我解释
- Oh, my god! - No, I can explain!
你还想着的不是卡洛琳  是加比
It's not Caroline you're still hung up on, it's Gabi.
不不不  好吧  不是这样
No! No, no, no, no. Okay, no, no, no.
你不明白
You don't understand.
那留言之所以在我电脑里
The reason why that's on my laptop,
是因为我从她手机里删掉了
is because I took it off her phone.
你看  我不想她听见
See, I didn't want her to listen to
因为我跟你在一起很开心
it because I'm so happy with you.
所以  你对加比没有感觉吗
So, you don't have feelings for Gabi?
我也是这么想的
That's what I thought.
乔什  你很可爱  也是个好男人
Josh, you are adorable and a good man,
但我不做第二名
But I am never runner-up.
别走
Don't go.
我没事的
I'll be fine.
再见  乔什
Goodbye, Josh.
再见  加比  吉莉
Goodbye, Gabi. Jilly!
我可以去当泊车员
I could be a valet parker.
是吗  你会开手动档吗
Really? Can you drive a stick?
不会
No.
你会平行泊车吗
Can you parallel park?
不会
No.
那你能当泊车员吗
Then, can you be a valet parker?
不能
No.
天啊  怎么回事  之前一切都那么完美
God, what happened? Everything was so perfect.
我在中国玩得那么高兴  和库珀那么幸福
I had an amazing time in China, I had a great time with Cooper,
我还有工作
I had a job.
加比  我是乔什  想跟你聊聊
Hey, Gabi, it's Josh, I need to talk to you.
说吧  说完拉倒
Go ahead. Get it over with quick.
我被开除了  是吗
I'm fired, right?
你没被开除
You're not fired.
你为什么不开除我  我自己都想开除自己
How could you not fire me? I would fire me!
我连鸡肉馅饼都没一般人做得好吃
I can't even cook a pot pie better than a civilian.
加比  够了
Gabi, stop.
我是故意选她的
I picked hers on purpose.
想得美  那是盲品好吗
Nice try. It was a blind taste test.
我能尝出来哪个是你的
And I knew which one was yours.
-怎么会  -酥皮里加了培根
- How? - Bacon in the crust.
典型的加比风格
Signature Gabi move.
还有  不加洋葱  因为我不喜欢
Also, no onions, 'cause I hate them.
多加了豆子  因为我很喜欢
Extra peas, 'cause I love them.
你是尝出来了
You did know.
那你为什么还选她的
Well, then why did you pick hers?
为了跟她上床
For the sex reasons.
我之前只是想跟吉莉能合拍一点
I just really wanted things to work out with Jilly.
什么叫"之前想"  怎么了
What do you mean "wanted"? What happened?
我们分手了
We broke up.
什么  为什么
What! Why?
她不喜欢我的歌
She didn't like my music.
我还觉得又找个"女朋友"
And I also think that maybe it was a little too soon for me
有点太急了
to have a "girlfriend."
乔什
Aww, Josh.
总有天  你会找到不用
Someday, you're gonna find a girlfriend
这样比划的女朋友的
you don't have to put quotes around.
一个你觉得不可思议的女朋友
I mean, somebody who's incredible for you,
百分百的懂你  还最好不会做饭
who totally gets you, and who, hopefully, can't cook.
-你这么觉得吗  -是的
- You think so? - Yeah.
你会找到完美的那个人的
You're gonna find somebody who's perfect for you.
就像我和库珀
Just like me and Cooper.
就像你和库珀
Just like you and Cooper.
没错
Yeah.
你想看我和库珀去中国玩拍的照片吗
Hey, do you want to see pictures of my trip to China with Cooper?
一点都不想
Not even a little.
好了  我刚写好了分手短信
Okay, I just finished my breakup text.
这样行不行
How does this sound?
乔治  真的很高兴遇见你
George, it was really nice to meet you,
但是我要说实话
but I have to be honest,
我只剩三个月能活了
I have three months to live.
让你看到这么美好的我  却又再夺走
And it will be cruel to give you so much,
真是残忍
only to take it away.
很好  非常好
It's good, really really good.
所以你觉得他不会很伤心吗
So you don't think he'll be too crushed?
不  我觉得他会没事的
Uhhh... no, I think he'll be okay.